CAO NGUYEN THANH NHI

Date of birth May 29th, 1995

Address **78/21/64 Street No.11, Ward 11,**

Go Vap District, Ho Chi Minh city

Cell phone **0906 956 562**

Email thanhi2905@gmail.com



Personal Statement

My university education and part-time work experience have prepared myself to meet high level qualifications for medical representative, which is what most employers expect these days.

I strongly believe that being able to work for pharmaceutical company would offer me chances of promoting and improving myself within a professional and dynamic environment. Furthermore, working with motivational teammates would inspire me to fulfill respective responsibilities in corporate environment and to achieve objectives in workplace.

Education

University of Medicine and Pharmacy at Ho Chi Minh city Bachelor of Pharmacy

9/2013-11/2018

Work Experience

Pharmacity drugstore

10/2017

Pharmacy intern

- Arranging and stocking shelves with medicines and other medical products.
- Assisting pharmacist in answering drug information questions.

Dottie store - local designer brand

4/2018-8/2018

Sale assistant

- Giving advice and guidance on product selection to customers.
- Ensuring high levels of customer satisfaction through excellent sales service.
- Being responsible for dealing with customer complaints.
- Keeping up to date with special promotions and putting up displays.

Home tutor 2014- 2016

• Monitoring student performance and assisting students in academic environments, such as classrooms or English centers.

Extracurricular activities

The volunteer campaign of Pharmacy students

Volunteer

- Taking part in outside activities to welcome freshmen of Medicine and Pharmacy University in Ho Chi Minh city.
- Participating in preparation and follow-up activities for Pharmacy yearly camp.

Daklak catholic students association in Ho Chi Minh city

Volunteer

- Helping students, especially freshmen to deal with housing issues.
- Conducting lifestyle workshops and camping programs to extend intellectual and social development in an outside school environment
- Setting up charity activities.

Certification

English

IELT 5.5 (Reading 7.0)

Skills

- Soft skills: Teamwork, communication skill, ownership, problem-solving, time management.
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint).